{"data":[{"question":"In the United States ________ is the most concentrated is New Orleans.","a":"French influence the city","b":"the city where French influence","c":"where the city influences French","d":"where the French influence the city","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Relative pronoun must stand after the noun\/pronoun it replaces.\n- Where= the city.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"A log grabber has a long arm ________, which stretches out to pick up logs.","a":"calls a jib","b":"calling a jib","c":"a jib called","d":"called a jib","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use past participle to shorten the clause \u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"A home computer ________ an opportunity for convenient and efficient work at home.","a":"provides","b":"to be providing","c":"which provides","d":"providing it","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- S (A home computer) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Eli Whitney's milling machine remained unchanged for a century and a half because ________ was so efficient.","a":"it","b":"he","c":"of","d":"its","answer":"1","explain":"\n- It= Eli Whitney's milling machine.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Some of the rainwater from clouds evaporates before ________.","a":"reaching the ground","b":"to reach the ground","c":"reach the ground","d":"the ground reaches","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Before + Verb_ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Once an offending allergen has been identified ________ tests, it is possible for the doctor to give specific desensitizing injections.","a":"means of","b":"by means of","c":"of the means by","d":"by means","answer":"2","explain":"\n- By means of something: using a particular method or system.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Sometimes ________ wears people out and is worse than the lack of sleep itself.","a":"to sleep the desire","b":"the desire to sleep","c":"to desire sleep is","d":"the desire to sleep who","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O = we need a Subject in ...\n- The desire to sleep: plays as a noun phrase.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Although dissimilar in almost every other respect, birds and insects have both evolved efficient ________ capabilities.","a":"fly","b":"flying","c":"to fly","d":"is flying","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Efficient ............. capabilities is a noun phrase- we need an adj or a noun in ....","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The wheel, ________ has remained important for 4,000 years, is one of mankind's first inventions.","a":"how","b":"when","c":"which","d":"about","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Which: is a relative pronoun used to replace for thing (When: time; how: manner).\u00a0\n- About + Noun\/ verb-ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"________ children master the basics, advanced development becomes easier.","a":"The","b":"Once","c":"That","d":"Even","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Once (conj): from the time when something happens.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}